Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Huh?
Unidentified male, appears to be in his mid-thirties,
What a tragedy.
hit by a truck, unconscious and in critical condition.
He's done for.
The driver of the truck is unhurt.
Oh yeah, I was hit by a...
Two high school students thought to have also been hit are currently missing.
A search is underway.
Requesting immediate backup. Over.
Did those three make it out okay?
He's heavy! Be careful!
Heh. You bet I am.
I've been a recluse for 20 years,
the type that bangs on the floor for food.
Zenith! Anipa bayhebu! La took!
Hm?
Do you know where you are?
Pipe down. You don't have to shout.
Epabuhia! Akunaja taku! La took!
Huh? What?
Blood pressure dropping!
Prepare a transfusion!
Can you hear me?
Do you know your name?
Can you speak?
Huh? Am I dying?
Oh well, my life was basically over anyway.
I wish I could've at least lost my virginity.
Epabuhia! Tauwka seio kwa! Pahail za!
Ivin kav Zenith! Pahail za!
Ow, my eyes!
Am I still alive?
Zevaiah bazalfben kifu zivaikah kwav!
Hey, who's this guy?
Seriously?
I'm 100-plus kilos, and he lifted me like...
Bukay aiha naiboo!
Whoa! What the hell?!
Stop! That's gross!
What the hell? Give me a break.
Zenith, tipen, eyuji, tawka paihail kwa.
Whoa.
What's she blushing like that for?
Her tits are huge.
Evun on. Nora iv aihen kap.
What language is that?
Wait, where am I? This isn't a hospital?
What the hell is he doing?
I'm seriously injured.
Still, she's gorgeous.
Is she European?
If you leave yourself that open,
I might cop a feel.
Huh?
It looks like I got reincarnated.
I can't believe something
that crazy happened for real.
Paul and Zenith. In their mid-20s, I'd guess.
Moraiha kwa.
Zai.
Tawkah, za iksalaib.
I'm 34, so they're practically kids to me.
Zevaika vawksay Rudy!
I'm seriously jealous of them,
making babies at their age.
Still, getting to suck on
a hottie's tits for free rules.
It didn't turn me on, though.
Maybe 'cause she's my mom?
Rudy?
Where are you?
Rudeus?
I guess my name's "Rudeus."
After six months, I've got
a pretty good grip on the language.
Maybe it's because I'm young,
but I feel like I learn weirdly fast.
Lilia the maid.
She's wonderfully endowed.
Hey, Rudy!
You shouldn't wander around on your own.
This doesn't go on your head.
What's wrong, Lilia?
Lady Zenith, this is
a little difficult to say, but...
Well...
I believe Master Rudeus may be afflicted by some sort of...
I'm sorry. Please forget I said anything.
Whatever could be so hard to say?
He's a child.
He doesn't know any better.
It's just...
What a view.
I've seen photos like this.
Is this Europe, like I thought?
Still,
Do you think this is enough?
it's definitely way too rural.
Yes.
You handle that, then, Lilia.
No electricity or gas? What year is it?
Of course, mistress.
I might be reborn, but I still
want to play with a computer.
Hey, what?
What's he doing?
Oh crap.
Rudy?!
Rudy!
Young Master!
Is he all right?
You're not supposed to move
people who've hit their heads, lady.
Even after that, he isn't crying.
There, there.
Just in case,
I'll cast a spell to make the pain go away.
Divine power is rich and nourishing.
Hey, are you kidding me?
It offers the strength to rise again
This is this country's
version of kissing a boo boo?
to those who have lost their strength.
Are both my parents delusional nerds?
Did the fighter marry the cleric?
Healing.
Well? It doesn't hurt anymore, right?
You wouldn't know it,
but Mommy used to be an adventurer.
What happened?!
I heard a loud...
Dear! Rudy fell on his head and—
Calm down. He's a kid.
Of course he'll fall down sometimes.
Besides, if he gets hurt, you can just heal him.
Don't tell me I'm in...
But what if he gets hurt
so badly that I can't heal him?
It'll be fine.
Actually, this pretty much confirms it.
This isn't Earth. It's another world.
A world of sword and sorcery.
I'm steady on my feet now.
Still, magic, huh?
Magic...
That's a word that'd get even a monkey excited.
I want to try it out myself ASAP.
That said, there's not much I can do right now.
Books?
There are only five books in the house.
Either books are expensive in this world,
or Paul and Zenith aren't big readers.
I used to have nearly a thousand,
so it's hard to believe.
All light novels, though.
I can't read it. I'll have
to learn to read first.
About another year passed.
Even with just five books, with the
help of Paul reading to me sometimes,
I can more or less read now.
Although I do wonder if he expects
a baby to understand what's in these books.
But man, this book is fascinating.
The Magic Manual.
I've seen some of this stuff in my old life.
Like, there are two ways to activate magic:
incantations and magic circles,
but incantations dominate
the mainstream right now, etc.
Seems like a deep system.
But I'm more concerned that, according to this,
your magic power is
basically set in stone at birth.
I'm worried.
I doubt my genes are going to put in much work.
Well, I guess I'll give it a shot.
Umm... Let the great protection
of water be on the place thou seekest.
I call a refreshing,
burbling stream here and now.
Water Ball.
Shouldn't it go flying?
One more try.
It's like practicing combos in a fighter.
Concentrate, picture it over
and over in your head,
then actually do it.
I didn't do the incantation yet.
What gives?
Huh?
This is all the MP I've got?
Honestly, Rudy.
If you're sleepy, you should go
to the bathroom and then to bed.
Damn it.
I'm too old for them to be thinking I wet the bed!
Damn it. Damn it!
Huh?
I experimented for a while and learned a lot.
That book's full of it!
Magic power grows the more you use it,
and magic works without incantations.
I guess I can't believe everything I read.
But if it's this easy,
what's even the point of incantations?
Maybe incantations are
a system for automating magic.
Holy Millis who watches
over us in distant lands,
we thank you for blessing us
with life-giving nourishment.
They do it all for you without
the need to focus on every single spell.
Time to eat!
If so, there's a big advantage to them.
First, they're easy to teach.
An incantation is all you need to cast,
so as magic was taught,
maybe over time people started
to think incantations were necessary.
Second, convenience.
Attack magic is probably used in combat,
Thus, Perugius led his
12 followers to the Devil Laplace.
and saying an incantation fast would
be quicker than closing your eyes to focus.
I think it's your bedtime now, Rudy.
Dear, I can't take any more!
I'm just getting started.
My growing magic power is another mystery.
Could it be the result of my training?
There's supposed to be a cap on
magic power, even if you work at it.
No, it's too soon to draw conclusions.
Yes. It could increase
as I grow up, for example.
Or maybe using magic at an early age
dramatically increases my maximum.
I shouldn't discount the
possibility that I'm unique.
I've gotten into this!
Whoops. That's no good. Cool it.
If that hypothesis is right,
there's only one thing to do:
Train as much as I can while I'm still growing.
Okay!
Still, how do I make these fly?
What?
Yes! All right!
I finally cracked how this incantation works.
This spell goes: create, set size,
set firing speed, activate.
That's the process it follows.
At least, I'm pretty sure that's it.
I never set the firing speed,
so it didn't go anywhere.
I've got more magic power now,
so it's time I tried intermediate magic.
Umm...
Supple spirit of water and princess
of streams that flow through the earth,
sweep away all things
with your hidden inner might.
Splash Flow.
What happened?!
H-Hey!
What's going on?
Rudy?!
Rudy!
Are you hurt?!
N-No.
Was it a monster?
No, around here there aren't...
Oh?
Rudy, did you read this book out loud?
Huh? Scary.
What's that look?
Maybe kids who use magic are dangerous
and get sent off to an inquisition?
No! Don't burn me at the stake!
I'm sorry.
Did you hear that, dear?!
I knew our boy was a genius!
Hang on. This is an intermediate—
Let's hire a magic tutor right now!
But wait, we haven't even taught him to re—
I'm sure he'll grow up to be an amazing mage!
Wait a minute! We promised that
if it were a boy, he'd be a swordsman.
But he can do intermediate magic at his age!
A promise is a promise!
You're one to talk!
You break yours all the time!
This has nothing to do with me!
Why not teach him magic in the morning
and swordsmanship in the afternoon?
It's not good to fight
in front of the baby, dear.
I guess not.
And so, we decided to hire me a magic tutor.
Paul spends all day at home swinging his sword,
but he's technically a knight
put in charge of this village.
I guess that's why he can
afford a tutor for a kid like me.
But this is the sticks on
the edge of the country.
Will anyone actually apply out here?
Or so I worried, but they found one in no time.
My parents expected
a retired adventurer to apply.
Good day.
So, we figured on a middle-aged
or old man with a big, bushy beard,
Good day.
a veteran spellcaster who really screams "mage."
I'm Roxy Migurdia.
Pleased to meet you.
What the hell?
Forget a beard; she looks like
her bush hasn't grown in yet.
Maybe middle-school age?
Loli, scornful gaze, unsociable:
three traits that equal perfection.
I want to marry her.
Oh, you're the, um... home tutor?
You're awfully, well...
She's tiny!
You're a fine one to talk.
Maybe she's sensitive about it?
I didn't mean her chest, though.
So, where is the student I'll be teaching?
Oh, he's right here!
You do see them sometimes.
Idiot parents who think their kid has
talent just because he's an early bloomer.
We can hear you, Roxy!
Looks like this one's a dud.
Excuse me?
Nothing!
Only, I doubt that child could
comprehend the theory of magic.
Don't worry! Our little Rudy is amazing!
I understand. I'll do what I can.
Huh? We're doing it outside?
Naturally.
In broad terms, there are
only three types of magic.
Attack magic, healing magic,
and summoning magic.
Each is divided into seven ranks: beginner, intermediate, advanced, sacred, royal, imperial, and divine.
And to use magic, you need magical power.
Either the magical power within you, or...
Is something wrong?
Oh, no.
All right, then.
Anyway, I'll start by demonstrating
an incantation, so repeat after me.
Do you need the incantation?
Of course you do.
I thought so.
Let the great protection of water
be on the place thou seekest.
I call a refreshing,
burbling stream here and now.
Water Ball!
What do you think?
Miss, my mom worked hard to raise
that tree, so I think she'll get mad.
Huh?
Th-That won't do, will it?
Divine power is rich and nourishing.
It offers the strength to rise again
to those who have lost their strength.
Healing!
Oh, wow.
You can use healing magic, too!
Yes, up to intermediate level.
Wow! That's amazing!
No, anyone can do as much
if they train properly.
A little praise goes right to her head.
Now, you try it.
Okay!
The Magic Manual didn't mention
incantation-less spells either.
I'd been using them without thinking,
but maybe that's taboo.
Roxy said you need incantations, too,
so I should say them for now.
They could be important.
Let the great protection of water
be on the place thou seekest...
What are you doing?
Oh, n-nothing!
How did I do?
You cut the incantation short.
I did.
Do you always abridge it like that?
I usually... just skip it.
Skip it?!
So, you usually omit the incantation.
I see.
It looks like you'll be worth training.
Oh.
Roxy! Don't use my trees as test subjects!
Huh?!
Oh, honestly!
I screwed up right away.
I guess I'll be fired tomorrow.
I'm sorry, miss. It was my fault.
Damn it. I went almost 20 years without having a conversation.
I don't know what to say at times like this.
No, think. You've done this lots of times.
Channel the main character of your favorite 18+ dating sim!
You didn't screw up, miss.
You gained experience.
I-I suppose so.
Thank you very much.
Ow!
More importantly, Roxy.
Y-Yes?
Let's go inside.
Let's start by introducing ourselves, okay?
Hey!
Hurry up!
I'm grateful, but I have
nothing to offer you in return.
Don't be silly.
Now, come on in.
You too, Rudy.
Okay!
Okay, let's get Roxy's welcome party started!
It's like a dream.
A dream I'm having as I die from that crash.
No.
Even if it is, I don't care.
In this world, I bet even I can make it.
If I live and try as hard as everyone else,
get back up when I fall,
and keep facing forward...
Maybe I can do it.
Maybe even I...
Maybe even a jobless, reclusive bum like me
can get a do-over at life,
and can get serious about living.
Episode 1
Jobless Reincarnation
Next time
Master